(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-13T21:35:30.080933",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
離れないで
Don't leave me...
ここに宣言します
Here I declare,
誓うよ愛する
I vow to love you.
病める時も
In sickness
健やかなるときも
and in health,
ずっと愛を歌い続けることを
I proudly vow to always
堂々と誓います
keep singing of my love.
歌もダンスももっと追求します
I'll keep striving to improve my singing and dancing,
ずっと推してもらえるアイドルになってみせます
and prove I can be an idol you'll support forever.
どんな不安な未来も私が照らすんだ
I will light up even the most uncertain future.
それでも落ち込んじゃう日は
Even so, on days I feel down,
思い出しているよ
I remember
みんなのその笑顔 その声を
everyone's smiles and voices.
HAPPY LUCKY 7 革命
HAPPY LUCKY 7 Revolution,
Sunday Monday
この先ずっと一緒だよね
we'll be together forever, right?
約束
Promise me.
ほらね 笑う門には福来たる
See? Good fortune comes to those who smile.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY 毎日がほら
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, look, every day is
Tuesday Wednesday LUCKY DAY
Tuesday, Wednesday, a LUCKY DAY.
生まれ変わっても迷わずに
Even if I'm reborn, without hesitation,
君だけのアイドルになるよ
I'll become an idol just for you.
何度も見つけてね
Find me again and again,
誓うよ愛する
I vow to love you.
アイドルとは時にあざとくが
They say being an idol means playing coy at times,
お決まりと誰かが言ってたけど
that's the rule, or so someone said,
上手くできないので
but I'm no good at that, so...
ねえ 睦まじ私からお願い聞いて
Hey, please listen to my fond request...
そして相思相愛
And let me ask for mutual love,
推し変なんてしないでよね
don't switch your favorite, okay?
私を見て
Look only at me.
HAPPY LUCKY 7 革命
HAPPY LUCKY 7 Revolution,
Sunday Monday
「みんなー！」
"Everyone!"
「楽しさに釣られ」
"Drawn in by the fun,"
「うっかり探したら」
"I carelessly looked around,"
「知らないあれやこれ」
"and came across all kinds of unknown things,"
「巡り会った」
"discovering them."
「大変な挑戦も」
"Tough challenges,"
「のんびり休息も」
"and relaxing rest, too."
「支え合って思い」
"Supporting each other, our feelings..."
「伝心した」
"...connected hearts."
「未開拓でも 前を向いて」
"Even in uncharted territory, looking ahead,"
「小さな星 重ねて」
"layering small stars."
「めぐったタイム」
"Through the times we've passed,"
「とぎれない」
"never-ending..."
「笑い声の中を進んでこう」
"...let's keep moving forward amidst laughter."
「さあ教えて ほら全部」
"Come on, tell me everything!"
「何回 時計の針」
"No matter how many times clock hands..."
「ぐるぐる回っても」
"...spin round and round,"
「話を聞くよ」
"I'll listen to your story."
「まだまだ終わらない」
"It's far from over!"
「この夢がひとつ」
"This single dream,"
「ずっと 永遠に」
"forever and always,"
「褪せることのない」
"never fading—"
「時代(とき)を君に送る」
"sending this era to you."
「訪れた先で」
"Wherever we go,"
「歓迎増えていく」
"welcomes keep growing."
「すれ違った風に」
"In the passing breeze,"
「聴いたみたい」
"it felt like I heard it."
「そして世界中を」
"And drawing the whole world in,"
「巻き込んで願う日」
"on this day of wishing,"
「一人また一人」
"one by one,"
「加わった」
"more joined in."
「超がんばったよって」
"Saying, 'I worked super hard!'"
「街中を探す」
"Searching through the town..."
「望遠鏡覗いても」
"Even looking through a telescope,"
「もう分からない」
"I still don't know."
「迷っているのも」
"Even being lost..."
「それが醍醐味なんだって」
"...that's the best part of it!"
「言っていこう」
"Let's keep saying that."
「ねぇねぇ」
"Hey, hey,"
「たくさんの思い出を」
"so many memories,"
「抱え抱きしめて」
"holding and embracing them tight,"
「宝物を大切に」
"cherishing our treasures,"
「運び続ける」
"we keep carrying them on."
「出会えた瞬間に」
"The moment we met,"
「こんな場所があるんだって」
"realizing a place like this exists,"
「パッと広げ」
"opening wide,"
「見せ続けていこう」
"let me keep showing it to you."
「次は君のもとへ」
"Next, straight to you!"
「ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！」
"Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!"
そら 教えで ほら 全部
Tell me everything, look, all of it
何回 時計の針 ぐるぐる回っても 話を聞くよ
No matter how many times the clock hands spin round and round, I'll listen to you.
OH まだまだ終わらない この
Oh, this isn't over yet, this...
夢がきっとずっと 永遠に
dream will surely, forever, eternally...
褪せることのない 時を
time that never fades,
君に贈る ねえ
I'll gift to you, hey.
みんな最後まで楽しんでいってね！
Everyone, enjoy until the very end!
急に成り立ての僕が
I, who suddenly just became who I am,
揺れるバッグ ぎゅっと抱えて
hold tightly onto my swaying bag.
夕日が沈むけど
Although the sun is setting,
君にだけは胸を張りたいよ
I want to stand proud, especially for you.
届くかな
Will it reach you?
一緒に行けるかな
Can we go together?
秘密のマッチを
Let's hand over...
渡していこう
...the secret match.
深呼吸をして
Taking a deep breath,
分かったこと
what I realized,
そう 盛大に
yes, let's laugh out loud...
笑っちゃおうかい
...in a big, grand way.
最高の一ページを
Making the best page,
上手くいかないことだって正解にして
turning even things that don't go well into correct answers.
明日の教科書 無視して閉じたら
If I ignore and close tomorrow's textbook,
何だってやれそうだ
I feel like I can do anything.
落書きの中に光ってた思いを
The thoughts that sparkled within the doodles,
君とこうして話せたんだって
that I could talk with you like this about them...
誇りたいから
because I want to be proud of that,
もっと
more,
まだ体験させて
let me experience even more.
ずっと
Forever...
大好きな感情のまま行こう
Let's move forward holding onto this feeling of love.
楽しかった意味をほら
Look, the reason it was so much fun,
一瞬でいこう
let's go in a flash!
昨日よりも加速してる
Accelerating even faster than yesterday,
ちゃんと繋いでて
keep holding on tight to me.
簡単じゃない
It's not simple,
僕の掛け声は
but my call...
いつも君が明るくなって
...you always brightened up
支えてくれた
and supported me.
ずっと
Forever,
満たされていくよ
I am being fulfilled.
みんな一緒に！せーの！
Everyone together! Ready, go!
上手くいかないことだって
Even when things don't go well,
どこだって行った
no matter where we went,
明日の教科書 水に流したら
if we wash tomorrow's textbook away,
何だってやれそうだ
I feel like I can do anything.
落書きの中に光ってた思いを
The thoughts that sparkled within the doodles,
君とこうして通じ合えたんだって
that I could connect with you like this over them...
誇りたいから
because I want to be proud of that,
もっと
more,
まだ体験させて
let me experience even more.
みんな笑顔で！
Everyone, with a smile!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
せーの！
Ready, go!
「おはよう！」 朝日に向かいご挨拶
"Good morning!" Greeting the morning sun,
ってあれ！？ 嘘！？ もうこんな時間！？
Wait, what?! No way! Is it this time already?!
午後から予定あるのに すぐに身支度をしなきゃ
I have plans this afternoon, I gotta get ready right away!
「行ってきまーす！」
"I'm off!"
慌てて飛び出して気づく
Rushing out in a hurry, I realize...
こっちじゃない！ ここどこ！？ たすけて あんきも〜
Not this way! Where am I?! Help me, Ankimo~!
トラブルばっか
Nothing but trouble,
転んで起きての毎日です
falling down and getting back up every day.
なんでも思い通りとか そんな美味しい話はないけど
Things don't always go as planned, there's no sweet deal like that,
心の中の曇り空を
but if I can chant the magic phrase
晴らす合言葉
that clears the cloudy skies in my heart...
唱えられたね？ ほら、快晴でしょ？
see, it's clear skies now, right?
ずっとみんなに届けたい
I want to deliver to everyone forever—
歌もダンスも元気も
songs, dances, and energy.
きっと同じ空の下
Surely under the same sky,
笑顔も分け合えるよ
we can share our smiles.
ちょっと疲れちゃうときも
Even when we get a little tired,
涙が出そうなときも
or when tears are about to fall,
いつもの魔法の言葉
with that usual magic phrase,
今日もけせらせらの空
today again, it's a Que Sera Sera sky!
せーの！ けーせらせら！
Ready, go! Que Sera Sera!
「こんそめ～」
"Kon-some~"
今日も一日がんばろう
Let's do our best again today!
カメラにマイクに よし準備OK！
Camera, mic, alright, ready to go!
お水もちゃんとあるし
I've got my water ready,
備えさえあれば嬉しいね
as long as I'm prepared, I'm happy!
それじゃ 今日は何をしようかな
So, what shall I do today?
お歌に雑談に あ、コラボ比べ？
Singing, chatting, or maybe comparing collabs?
みんなと笑い合えば また明日も晴れ晴れだ
If I laugh together with everyone, tomorrow will be sunny again!
よっしゃー！
All right!
ほっと胸息こぼして
Letting out a gentle sigh,
ふと夜空を見上げたら
as I casually look up at the night sky,
満点の星たちが キラキラ瞬いていた
stars filling the sky were twinkling brightly.
ずっと追いかけ続けたい
I want to keep chasing forever,
雲より高い夢でも
even if it's a dream higher than the clouds.
もっと強く羽ばたいて
Flapping my wings even stronger,
空まで駆けてゆくよ
I'll run all the way up to the sky.
そっと背中押すような 温もりに包まれたら
Wrapped in a warmth that gently pushes my back,
いつまでも止まらないよ
I'll never stop.
今日も
Today,
明日も
and tomorrow,
ずっと
forever,
けせらせらの空
in the Que Sera Sera sky!
せーの！ けーせらせら！
Ready, go! Que Sera Sera!
みんなー！
Everyone~!
みんな！ 新年あけまして...
Everyone! Happy...
おめでとうございまーす！
...New Year!
本日はお寒いなか、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming today despite the cold!
みんな来れた？
Did everyone make it?
あ、来れてるから居るの分かって... ちゃんと安全に来れましたか？
Ah, you're here so I know you made it... Did you arrive safely?
今回のソロライブは 私のライブ史上最大規模ということで
This solo live is the largest in my concert history,
すごい大きな会場で ハッシュタグとかも見てたんだけど 「でかっ」って
at a huge venue. I was checking the hashtag and saw comments saying 'It's huge!'
「でかいな、すごいな」って書いてる人がいっぱいいて
So many people were writing 'It's huge, impressive!'
私も「でかいなー、すごいなー」と思いながら見てました
I was looking at it thinking, 'It's so big, so incredible!'
リハーサルの時は「ここにいっぱいそらまめさん来るね」って言われて
During rehearsal, they told me, 'A lot of Soramates will come here.'
「え、誰も居ないじゃん！ 誰も居ないよ！」っていう会話をしながら
And we were joking around like, 'Wait, there's no one here! No one's here!'
とても楽しくやっておりました！
We were having a lot of fun!
でもみんな居るね！ ありがとー！
But everyone is here! Thank you~!
というわけで、今日も初めてライブだよって人！
So then, who here is at my concert for the first time today?!
おー、結構居るね！
Oh, there are quite a few!
じゃあ、現地自体初めてだよって人！
Then, who here is attending an in-person concert for the very first time?!
結構居る！ ありがとう！
Quite a lot! Thank you!
じゃあ... 手振るだけでいいからね！ 女の子ー！
Then... you can just wave your hands, okay?! Girls~!
おー！ 声出してくれてありがとう！ きゃー！ 聞こえたー！
Ooh! Thank you for cheering! Kyaa! I heard you~!
男子ー！
Boys~!
おー！ ありがとうございます！
Ooh! Thank you so much!
これってあれ、ペンライトとかで出来んのかな？ 待って、出来ないのかな？
Wait, can we do that with lightsticks? Wait, can we not?
出来るかな？ こちらの人、赤！
Can we? People over here, red!
こちらの人は、青！
People over here, blue!
真ん中は、黄色！
In the middle, yellow!
うわ、すごい！
Wow, amazing!
綺麗！
So pretty!
こんな感じでですね
So, like this,
今日はペンライトでも遊べちゃうということで
you can have fun with your penlights today as well,
ぜひぜひみんなでも楽しんでいきましょう！
so let's all enjoy ourselves together!
今日はみんなも主役だよ！
Everyone is the star of the show today!
あれ？なんでないの？
Huh? Why aren't there any?
「水かわいい」？ありがとう！
"Water is cute"? Thank you!
もうちょっと飲むの？
Drink a bit more?
ねえ、ねえ…
Hey, hey...
水だって分かったじゃん、後ろ向いたから
You knew it was water because I turned around, right?
えー！ありがとう！
Yay! Thank you!
さあ、というわけでね、今日は「いかがだったでしょうか」とはいかないので
Now then, I can't really say "How was the show?" today,
始まったばかり！
because we're just getting started!
なんですが…
However...
なんと！もう言っていいのかな？
Guess what! Is it okay to say it now?
YouTubeの配信は…
The YouTube stream...
なんと、ここまでなんです！
...is actually ending here!
始まったばかりー！
We just started!
でも、続き見たい人は…
But for those who want to keep watching...
どこだろ？ここ、ここ、ここ…
Where is it? Around here, here, here...
ここらへんに、かな？
Maybe around here?
あの、チケットとか買えると…
Um, where you can get tickets...
「買える」って言い方あれだ…見に来てねー！
Ah, saying "buy" sounds weird... Come watch it, okay?
チカチカしとる、すごい！
It's flashing! Wow!
というわけで、先にどんどん行ってみましょうか！
So then, shall we keep moving forward?
盛り上がれますかー！？
Are you ready to get hyped?!
楽しんでいってねー！
Have fun!
それじゃあ、盛り上がっていこう！
Alright then, let's get fired up!
Oh ドキドキ 変数が理屈を…
Oh, doki doki... variables logic...
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
[The free preview stream ends here.]